Lorelle and I went shopping on Sunday for
our new apartment.  You can do the whole thing
in Herlen, Netherlands
, because there are so many of these
stores in one place.  First we went
to a decoration shop; they had all
sorts of decorations, lamps, but also some
furniture.  Then we went to Quantum.  This
is already super hyped on TikTok.   But
I have to say, I didn't find that
so great.  Yes, they did have some nice
decorative items.  I've
shown you those here too, but some of them were
very colorful and looked a bit
cheap.  Then I
saw this ultra cute doorstop at J's.  We
were in a shop where I
immediately fell in love with everything.  It was such
a dream.  They had beautiful
beds and sofas, and also incredibly beautiful
decorations, but unfortunately they were a bit more expensive.
Then we went to Zenox, or whatever the
store is called.  They had everything
imaginable, including kitchen utensils.  In the
end, we went to IKEA
and only
bought things there.